CHRISTIAN D. BARRIOS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

09615281824

Christianbarrios995@gmail.com

https://portfolio-silk-nu-17.vercel.app/

Brgy. Talacuan, Leon Iloilo

SKILLS

Intermediate: HTML, CSS, JS, React

Basic: Figma design, PHP, wordpress, Ruby on rails, Python, Node JS, Next JS, mySQL, MongoDb, Firebase

Tools: Github, vscode, notion, canva, figma, docker

EDUCATION

Computer Science

West Visayas State University

March 2015 - March 2019

Web development courses

Zuitt Bootcamp

June 2022 - August 2022

Programming Self Study

Online Courses

January 2020 - Present

PROFILE

I am a full-stack web developer based in Iloilo, Philippines. I can develop responsive and fun websites from scratch and raise them into modern user-friendly web experiences. Transforming my creativity and knowledge into apps has been my passion for more than a year. I have been helping various clients and fellow developers establish their presence online. I always strive to learn about the newest technologies and frameworks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software engineer

Sence1 ph

January 2023 - April 2024

- The design lead for our company website team
- I have been creating and maintaining responsive websites for our clients using front-end programming languages.
- I have created wireframes and designs for our service ideas with the help and feedback of the team.
- Contribute in creating responsive websites for our service idea using react with typescript.
- Contribute in making our company website using Wordpress custom theme.
- Conduct research and interviews for our service idea.
- Research, collaborate with the team and made documentations to make our coding standards.

Freelance web developer

LeChef Culinary School

September 2022 - January 2023

- Created responsive landing page for their website using the design given by their designer.
- Contribute in maintaining and testing their developer's project.
- Helped creating automation for creating their menus using python and mysql.

Software Analyst

Reed Elsevier

March 2020 - June 2022

- Responsible for checking if there are bugs or errors in the programmer's codes that might affect the output of their app.
- In charge of creating a manual that programmers can base their inputs, calculations and features of the programs.
- Compiled comprehensive documentation detailing how to replicate bugs and what conditions necessary for them to occur, providing valuable insights for programmers.